All you have to do is listen.
Monolith is a horror, mystery, science fiction film directed by Matt Vesely.
A desperate young journalist turns to podcasting to salvage her career, but
her rush to make headlines leads her to an alien conspiracy.
The Interviewer, played by Lily Sullivan.
Floramae (voice), played by Ling Cooper Tang.
Paula (voice), played by Ansuya Nathan.
Dad (voice), played by Erik Thomson.
Klaus (voice), played by Terence Crawford.
Laura (voice), played by Kate Box.
Monolith is a 2022 Australian science-fiction thriller film directed by Matt Vesely from
a script  written by Lucy Campbell, and produced by Bettina Hamilton.
Described as high-concept science fiction, it stars Lily Sullivan, the only
on-screen actor in the film, as a journalist uncovering a mystery.
The film premiered in Australia on 27 October 2022 at the Adelaide Film
Festival, and internationally at SXSW in March 2023.
The film explores themes of journalist, alien conspiracy, podcast.
The tone is intense and dark and thought_provoking.